* 

SFG\_Privacy Policy

1. [Home](https://sustainablefuturesglobal.org/)
2. SFG\_Privacy Policy

Sustainable Futures Global is a Community Interest Company (**SC783964** – not for profit) registered in Scotland. We collect personal information when you register with us, download resources, apply for a vacancy, purchase a service, or contact us. We will use this information to provide the services requested, ensure the validity of your request, maintain our records and, where appropriate, to send you marketing information. Sustainable Futures Global Community Interest Company will not share your information for marketing purposes with other companies.

You can contact us at any time to find out what information we hold on you. You can update, edit, view, and request we remove any data that we hold. There is some data we require to hold in order to provide our services and meet our own legal obligations but we will happily discuss all of this with you.

You can also opt out of communications, there is an unsubscribe option in every marketing communication we send, which will take you to your preferences centre. If you would like to unsubscribe please email info@sustainablefuturesglobal.org and we will unsubscribe you.

We take all reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure. We have in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

Sustainable Futures Global Community Interest Company will only process your data or communicate with you if one or more of the 6 lawful bases for processing data set out in Article 6 of the GDPR applies.

(a) Consent: you have given clear consent to process your personal data for a specific purpose.

(b) Contract: the processing is necessary for a contract we have with you, or because you have asked us to take specific steps before entering into a contract.

(c) Legal obligation: the processing is necessary for us to comply with the law (not including contractual obligations).

(d) Vital interests: the processing is necessary to protect someone’s life.

(e) Public task: the processing is necessary for you to perform a task in the public interest or for your official functions, and the task or function has a clear basis in law.

(f) Legitimate interests: the processing is necessary for our legitimate interests or the legitimate interests of a third party unless there is a good reason to protect the individual’s personal data which overrides those legitimate interests.

Candidates
----------

Sustainable Futures Global Community Interest Company will process candidate data for recruitment purposes only. We will store the data in our Applicant Tracking System and will not share this with anyone else outwith our company.

We will store your data for a period of 6 months and when this period is over we will delete your data within 1 month.

Candidates have the right to access data we have stored and can request for this to be rectified. Candidates can withdraw consent at any time.

### What information we hold about you

In connection with your application, we will collect, store, and use the following categories of personal information about you:

* The information you have provided to us in your curriculum vitae, covering letter and application form.
* The information you have provided on our application form, including name, title, address, telephone number, personal email address, date of birth, gender, employment history and qualifications.
* Any information you provide to us during an interview.
* Any information you provide to us during on boarding if you are successful in your application.

We may also collect, store and use the following “special categories” of more sensitive personal information:

* Information about your ethnicity
* Information about your health, including any medical condition, health and sickness records.
* Information about criminal convictions and offences.

### How we collect your data

We collect personal information about candidates from the following sources:

* You, the candidate.
* Recruitment agency, (if applicable) from which we collect the following categories of data: name, title, address, telephone number, personal email address, date of birth, gender, employment history and qualifications
* NGA uses a non-recorded enquiry through CIFAS credit reference agency, from which we collect the following categories of data: CCJs, bankruptcies or voluntary arrangements from the past 6 years. (regulated and senior positions only)
* NGA liaises with DBS and DBS Scotland, Disclosure and Barring Service in respect of unspent criminal convictions.
* Your named referees, from whom we collect the following categories of data: Company employed by, role performed, dates of employment, and reason for leaving.

### How we use your information

We will use the personal information we collect about you to:

* Assess your skills, qualifications, and suitability for the role.
* Carry out background and reference checks, where applicable.
* Communicate with you about the recruitment process.
* Keep records related to our hiring processes.
* Comply with legal or regulatory requirements.

This website uses Google Analytics and HubSpot Analytics to help analyse how visitors use the site. The tools use “cookies,” which are text files placed on your computer, to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including IP address) is transmitted to Google and HubSpot. This information is then used to run analytics on website visitors and to compile statistical reports on website activity for Sustainable Futures Global Community Interest Company.

We will never (and will not allow any third party to) use the statistical analytics tool to track or to collect any Personally Identifiable Information (PII) of visitors to our site. Google or HubSpot will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google or HubSpot. Neither we, Google, nor HubSpot will link, or seek to link, an IP address with the identity of a computer user. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any PII from any source, unless you explicitly submit that information via a fill-in form on our website.

You may choose to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically default to accept them, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings, then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

Visitors to our website are able to register to use our services, attend events, make a purchase, join a community or upload/download information. When you register, you will provide personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number and other relevant information. If you are making a purchase, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for your purchase. This information may be forwarded to your financial provider. We will not disclose Personally Identifiable Information (PII) we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary to fulfil your requests, to protect ourselves from liability, to comply with the terms and conditions of our internet host provider.

##### Navigate

##### Contact

info@sustainablefuturesglobal.org

© 2024 Sustainable Futures. All rights reserved

We use cookies from third party services for marketing activities and to offer you a better experience.  
Read about how we use cookies and how you can control them by clicking "Privacy Preferences".

Privacy Preferences

I Agree

### Privacy Preference Center

#### Privacy Preferences

When you visit any website, it may store or retrieve information through your browser, usually in the form of cookies. Since we respect your right to privacy, you can choose not to permit data collection from certain types of services. However, not allowing these services may impact your experience.

Privacy Policy

Required 

You read and agreed to our Privacy Policy.

CDN

Required 

For performance and security reasons, we use Cloudflare and MaxCDN as our CDN networks.

YouTube

We use the YouTube service to enable video content streaming on this site.

Vimeo

We use the Vimeo service to enable video content streaming on this site.

Hubspot

We use the Hubspot service to enable video content streaming on this site.
